Come on!
Throw her a hook!
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Hey, I'm made of way!
I'm made of way!
Ani-e-man-dai-kai-ke
Meidokissade-kako-ren-bo
Baito-ki-u-chi-tai-se-ya
Reku-ai-wa-no-no-ki-mi-no-hana-zo-no
Duh...
He did not have the figurine on him
He says he already sold it...
...to a man named Kijima
That's what he told me.
Um Ronco would um one of these help I
thought your hair might be in the way.
Uh you can take whichever one
you like I shall borrow this one.
No please you can have it
that's much appreciated.
Come to Oinkie Doink Cafe!
Please come visit our cafe, Master!
Hey, Nogomi.
Did something good happen?
Nerula!
Yes, I would say so.
Get out of our way, lowlifes!
Hey, man, a maid just
tried to give me a flyer.
I hope she doesn't try to kill me.
Oh, precious Gracie Poo,
what an unruly town this is!
Nerula, who are those people?
They're from an anime figurine company.
I've heard that they're known for
buying and selling premium figurines.
Show me the fake, Grace.
How lovely.
An amateur would never be
able to tell the difference.
We'll sell that one for a high price.
Sweet little Gracie Poole,
don't you worry at all.
I won't let anyone touch a
single hair on your head.
It's best if we stay far away from them.
What the hell do you want?
Wanting a rohamptic time?
Come to Oinky Doink Cafe.
You think I'm threatened
by some trashy maid?
I could take over your
cheesy cafe just like that.
Some trashy what?
Should the maids be initiating violence?
It's because I am a maid.
Huh.
You wouldn't understand.
I can't simply back down after
being insulted like that.
Maids should be cute by nature.
How dare you call yourself a maid?
You, foreigner.
Did Tyra send you here to collect me?
Yes, I am here to escort you, sir.
I refuse to acknowledge
you as a true maid.
Hey, are you okay?
You all look awfully vivacious
for a bunch of hogs that
haven't paid back any of the
honey money that you owe me.
Given how much trouble you've caused,
you can't possibly complain no matter
what kind of job we ask you to do.
Now let's get down to business.
Hey, how much water do
you expect me to drink?
I can't have all that
sloshing around in my gut.
You better stand back.
I'm gonna spew this shit out all over you!
But hold on now, that's quite an
impressive body you've got there.
Manager!
Yes, whatever you say!
I have something in mind that would be
perfect for your water-pouring porker.
Let's negotiate terms.
I bet it's another high-risk job.
No need to worry about a thing.
I can't call myself manager
if I can't protect my piglets.
One last thing.
The eggs left in the fridge, they're past
their expiration, but they're still good.
Hmm.
Um, where's Ronco, Chief?
She went straight to the venue.
We'd better head over there, too.
We'll cross Monsei Bridge, in the opposite
direction, towards a successful tomorrow!
So you made her take the job after all.
Huh?
But earlier you said a manager's
supposed to protect her staff.
The wind's blowing our way.
Ronko's on board, too.
Great.
So where are we going?
The Akiba Fluffy and Sweet Club.
Aw, how cute!
Is the job a live gig or something? Yeah.
One that pumps you chock
full of adrenaline.
Come on!
Throw her a hook!
Do you know how much I bet on you?
What?
This is the Akiba Fluffy and Sweet Club?
Okay, take your places.
Bronco!
Don't tell me you're going to fight!
I shall do my best.
What? No!
A maid shouldn't have to do this!
Fighting for the sake of her
cafe is what a maid does.
Ronco will lose in the
third round by knockout.
Without fail.
Exactly as you wish.
Ashtray.
Right here, madam.
I practice a special breathing technique.
Shit!
If you don't want an eye
patch on your other eye,
you'd better deliver on
your end of the deal.
Madam Taira, Kijima is here
to show you a new figurine.
You're rigging it?
Dude, that's so loud.
So does that mean we're just going
to lose and get paid for the fight?
Not just that.
We know the outcome as well.
So we'll bet on the
opponent and rake it in.
Honestly, our chiefs are real genius.
Ah, great.
I see a new face is up against the champ.
That intimidating presence.
This made Ronko looks promising.
The pure Mucky Masami's
the uncontested reigning
champion despite having those
beautiful delicate arms.
She's in peak condition to win a
third consecutive championship.
It's gonna be one hell of a fight!
Uncontested champion?
That girl?
I must say you're extremely fortunate,
Miss Tyra This item has never
been displayed on the open market.
We barely managed to
acquire this one ourselves.
Oh, my Gracie-poo!
Yes, Grace Inumata.
A character from the anime
Legendary Fighter Nobuaki.
She's one of my favorites, too.
Though still in grade school,
she's an exceptional mentor who
supports Nobuaki's development.
Her steadfast devotion inspired me
so much growing up as a young child.
But as you might know she's as minor as a
sub character can get there were very few
figurines made to begin
with and that scarcity
escalated her price
tremendously she's easily
going to fetch way beyond
10 million i'll pay
any price you want for
her it's only because
of my loyal admiration for her that i was
able to train our
starfighter to be a champion
All right!
Wait.
Why on earth did you win the fight?
Just barely.
In the first round?
With a single punch?
I said just barely.
What do you mean?
I told you a hundred times
to lose in the third round!
Now that I've been in the ring, I realize
I have difficulty pulling punches.
It's contrary to how I've lived my life.
How unusual.
Was the opponent unaware of the deal
you made earlier with her manager?
It must be tough creating a star in
a world where strength is everything.
In any case, let us
discuss the price for gold.
Seppo.
M-Madam.
This would have happened either way.
Now bring those damn pigs to me.
So, uh...
I'm asking if you have the ability to
comprehend what the hell you've done here.
I have a dream. Huh?
I want to move to Hawaii and buy a tiki
bar and be surrounded by pretty boys.
So please, give us another chance.
I'll get Ronko to beat everyone
and make it to the finals.
She'll totally wipe out the competition.
And why should I want that pig to win?
When the crowd is dead, sure, Ronko's
going to win it all and take it.
She'll get her ass whooped
in the final match.
That's the moment your fighter
will become a shining star.
Let us help you create a new sensation.
You can read the batch right probably
so you want to ring it right not
particularly just lose the finals
You got that right sure in theory.
What do you say ma 'am?
See how committed Ronko is to our plan?
Okay, fine get in here.
She's a sorry excuse for a maid.
She can't even smile, but she has fighting
skills from her military experience!
This dirty swan of yours can't win
even if she messes with the plan?
So you're a maid, too.
I simply dressed like I was a maid.
Neither you nor I are
real maids. Not true.
Once you put a uniform on, you have
the right to be a maid no matter what.
The only judge that determines if
you're a maid or not is yourself.
Okay, I'll go along with that
plan. Hey, you! Mistress Pig!
Take this body here and shove it in the
trunk of the car in the parking lot.
Understood.
And you why are you sitting
there naked I'm devoted
You still have to fight it was
my screw-up that brought us here
after all We'll cross Monsei
Bridge in the opposite direction,
towards a successful tomorrow.
You're scheming again, aren't you, Chief?
For the first step toward tomorrow.
Let's go.
Where are we?
These places loan you money and they'll
let you use your organs as collateral.
Organs?
We just have to win.
Anyway, you only need like
half a stomach to survive.
For real?
That's like borrowing money for free.
Hey, look.
They have a stomach and lung combo.
Amazing.
I'm witnessing a living legend
in the making right here.
It's the birth of a new star.
She has to really fight
her to rig the match?
You might as well cheer her on.
Ronko's having to break her neck in there.
Hey, ho-ho-ho!
Miss Tyra, have you seen our president?
He disappeared after you asked to see him.
I'm afraid he never showed
up for our appointment,
but we did find this
on our security camera.
Boss!
It's that same bitch!
Should we take her out?
That would interrupt the
tournament that's going on.
Let us handle this matter for you. Why?
I promise to satisfy your
thirst for vengeance.
In the final bout, gentlemen.
A dead maid tells no tales.
Today you will die with the blame for
this missing figurine on your shoulders,
Ronco Manon.
You've told Zoya to pummel
her to death, is that correct?
Yes, ma 'am, I have.
But Ronko Manon is requesting
an audience with you.
She says she has something to show you.
Tell her to go prepare for the fall.
The only judge that determines if you're
a maid or not can only be yourself.
When we give the signal, take her out.
Listen, only a monkey makes
the same mistake twice.
Take the punches that come
your way, and don't hit back.
No matter what happens,
you're going to lose.
You've got to take a dive.
Now don't forget, tell me, which round?
The 12th round.
That's right!
Perfect!
You got this!
You're a loser!
Now go out there and
take one for the team!
Sure thing.
Here it is.
The final match between
two monster rookies.
An MMA fight with 12 rounds.
That's just insane.
The odds are stacked
in Ronco Manon's favor,
but I doubt it'll play out that smoothly.
Damn it.
I don't have enough organs to
bet all the money I want to.
Lose the fight for the cafe.
For the cafe.
Impressive.
I can't see her punches.
So she has to keep taking
all those hard glows?
I'm not going to strike back.
Nice!
Very nice!
I can see tomorrow dawning.
Just keep this up till the end.
There's no way she can
do this for 11 rounds.
That damn woman.
You've got the go-ahead, so do it. Хорошо.
What?
Back of the head?
Hey, wait, that's a... a nut!
That's a nut shot!
No, that's not a nut shot.
What? Hey, referee!
Now die!
Rocco!
Hey, Ronko!
Were you about to hit her? No.
Maybe you should stop.
Looks like she was coming in for the kill.
She was not!
Ronko can do this!
I can see pretty boys in my future!
Don't you realize she's about to be
killed for some useless petty cash?
It's not a problem.
I won't be taking any more hits.
I can feel the wind!
The winds of Waikiki!
Are you okay?
Look at you better than one.
You call yourself a maid.
I'm an oinky-doink maid.
That said cafe is full of
nothing but wannabe maids. What?
Anyone who acknowledges you as a maid
must be total crap, just like you!
Stupid bitch.
Bronco, what the hell?
Only a monkey makes the same
mistake twice, you stupid bitch.
Stop that.
Get your paw off me.
How are you feeling?
I sincerely apologize.
Your hair tie is gone.
Do you have a spare one
in your paw, Tronco?
Oh, I have a spare one!
Sorry for the hassle.
Hey, what now?
Isn't this the...
So you're ready to fight me now?
You know you can't spin
on our cafe's good name.
And think that you'll get away with it!
Because I am a maid.
Hey, this wasn't the deal!
Those damn rotten pig heads!
Oh, crap! My pancreas!
My pancreas! Come on!
Please lose, Bronco!
What is her deal?
Did she really be called a maid?
I was always denied cute
things from an early age.
That was when I discovered
the world of maid
cafes and aspired to become a maid myself.
But the maids I envisioned in my
mind didn't reek of blood like this.
To me, they were all
brightness and sparkles.
And shining with so much
cuteness Yes, it was blinding.
So if I...
Is she smiling?
But I...
I...
You look great! Thanks.
Geez, can't you act cuter?
You're not cut out to be a cute cafe maid.
But I don't know how to smile.
I won't have it. Look at you.
You aren't cute at all.
You're wrong.
I am cute.
Especially today.
Because I'm wearing this adorable
hair tie that Nagomi gave me.
If I've been against her, will
that help me acknowledge myself?
If, like her, I can call myself cute?
Shall we?
Mister.
Please, Ronco.
Ranko!
Knock her out!
Ranko, you are very cute.
As are you.
Chiburashka.
Don't go.
What the?
Stop it! Don't do that!
Hey, Chris.
My spleen.
You pieces of shit!
Don't let those pigs out alive!
Huh?
We found this note posted on
your office door. Miss Tyra,
I would like to tell
you something about the
body you had me dump in
the trunk of the car.
That means our president was
here before he disappeared.
That means you must have killed him!
You two sold off your organs?
The pancreas is just decorative,
like window dressing.
So, hey, listen, guys.
Didn't that creepy Kijima guy make a
fortune off of selling premium figurines?
Apparently.
That's what I heard.
Well then, maybe we can sell this.
Well that was all for
nothing we didn't even
manage to pay off any of our overdue dues.
At least you should be
grateful you got to keep
all of your organs
bellyaching won't get us to?
Tomorrow piglets remember
striking it rich starts
one step at a time for
starters i got some extra Pig
power i'm soya i'm the new
maid joining oinky doink
starting today i'll do my
very best to to become a cute,
adorable maid.
Hey, from yesterday.
Are you really the same person?
This cute person is surreal through me.
An actual live overseas hire?
Tyra is dead.
I got her for free in the
deal, no strings attached.
We've finally gone international.
I'm a total novice with no knowledge
to speak of, but I'll do my very best.
So I'm counting on you to teach me, Ranko.
It's good to have you.
It's the only way I can't believe!
I can't believe it.
I can't
believe it.
You are the one who you are.